The Offering is a mystery, thriller, horror film directed by Kelvin Tong.
When young and successful reporter Jamie finds out that her sister has died in
mysterious circumstances, she travels to Singapore to uncover the truth.
There, she discovers multiple deaths linked to her sister's and must join forces with her sister's husband in
order to defeat a demonic entity that is using new technology to complete an ancient mission.
Sam Harris, played by Matthew Settle.
Jamie Waters, played by Elizabeth Rice.
May Wong, played by Pamelyn Chee.
Majorie Tan, played by Jaymee Ong.
Katie Harris, played by Adina Herz.
Fr. James De Silva, played by Colin Borgonon.
The Faith of Anna Waters is a 2016 American-Singaporean horror film starring American
actors Elizabeth Rice and Matthew Settle and directed by Kelvin Tong.
Billed as Singapore's first Hollywood supernatural feature, the film tells the story of an American journalist who travels to Singapore
to investigate the mysterious suicide of her sister, and delves into one of Tong's favourite horror subgenres: exorcism.
The film was released on 6 May 2016 in the United
States under the title The Offering.
The tone is intense and dark and mind_bending.